Department of Economics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Departmental committees, 1966 - 1979; F-8-4; 32 cm of textual records
  - Executive committee, 1969 - 1978; F-8-4-5; 4 cm of textual records
    - Executive committee, 1973 - 1978; F-8-4-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
  - Graduate Studies committee, 1971 - 1979; F-8-4-6; 2 cm of textual records
    - Graduate studies committee, 1971; F-8-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1976 - 1979; F-8-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
  - Nominations committee, 1968 - 1977; F-8-4-7; 3 cm of textual records
    - Nominations committee, 1968 - 1972; F-8-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Nominations committee, 1973 - 1974; F-8-4-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Nominations committee, 1975 - 1977; F-8-4-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
  - Planning and priorities committee, 1972 - 1979; F-8-4-8; 4 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Business. Planning and Priorities Committee
    - Planning and priorities committee, 1972 - 1974; F-8-4-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Planning and priorities committee, 1975 - 1977; F-8-4-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Planning and priorities committee, 1978; F-8-4-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-22)
    - Planning and priorities committee, 1978 - 1979; F-8-4-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
  - Tenure committee, 1966 - 1975; F-8-4-9; 3 cm of textual records
    Access to records in the subseries "Appointment" and "Tenure" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
    - Tenure committee, 1966 - 1971; F-8-4-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
    - Tenure committee, 1972 - 1975; F-8-4-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
  - Undergraduate curriculum committee, 1967 - 1979; F-8-4-10; 3 cm of textual records
    - Undergraduate curriculum committee, 1967 - 1976; F-8-4-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
    - Undergraduate curriculum committee, 1977 - 1979; F-8-4-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
  - Ad hoc committee, 1968 - 1974; F-8-4-11; 1 cm of textual records
    - Ad Hoc committees, 1968 - 1974; F-8-4-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
  - Departmental committees, 1969 - 1978; F-8-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-21)
- University committees, 1976 - 1980; F-8-5; 3 cm of textual records
  Series consists of departmental files relating to the Articulation Committee and University Review Committee of the Faculty of Arts. Series includes memoranda, minutes, and correspondence.
  University Review Committee
  - Articulation meetings, 1976 - 1980; F-8-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
  - University review committee, 1977 - 1978; F-8-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
- Departmental reviews, 1968 - 1980; F-8-6; 12 cm of textual records
  Series consists of materials relating to external and faculty reviews of the Department. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - External reviews, 1975 - 1976; F-8-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
  - External reviews - papers, 1975; F-8-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-23)
  - External reviews - papers, 1972 - 1975; F-8-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
  - Departmental status - retreat, 1976; F-8-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
  - Faculty status review, 1968; F-8-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
  - Faculty status review, 1973; F-8-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
  - Faculty status review, 1974 - 1975; F-8-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
  - Faculty status review, 1976 - 1980; F-8-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
- Course outlines and exams, 1967 - 1984; F-8-7; 89 cm of textual records
  Series consists of files of undergraduate and graduate course outlines and examinations.
  - Economics 100-3, 1970 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
  - Economics 101-3, 1970 - 1979; F-8-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-24)
  - Economics 102-3, 1972 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Commerce 103-3, 1972 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Economics 150-3, 1970 - 1977; F-8-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Economics 152-3, 1973 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Economics 200-3, 1970 - 1975; F-8-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Economics 200-3, 1976 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Economics 201-3, 1973 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Commerce 203-3, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Economics 205-3, 1968 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 8-25)
  - Economics 205-3, 1975 - 1984; F-8-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 208-3, F-8-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Commerce 221-3, 1978 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Commerce 223-3, 1972 - 1973; F-8-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Commerce 223-3, 1973 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 231-3, 1978 - 1979; F-8-7-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Commerce 235-3, 1968 - 1969; F-8-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 235-, 1969 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 236-, 1971 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 280-, 1973 - 1979; F-8-7-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 293-, 1973 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 301-, 1970 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 8-26)
  - Economics 302-, 1972 - 1976; F-8-7-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Commerce 303-, 1970 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Economics 304-, 1972 - 1976; F-8-7-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Economics 305-, 1970 - 1981; F-8-7-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Economics 308-, 1972 - 1975; F-8-7-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Economics 309-, 1974; F-8-7-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Economics 310-, 1970 - 1982; F-8-7-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Economics 313-, 1971 - 1975; F-8-7-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Commerce 322-, 1973 - 1976; F-8-7-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Commerce 323-, 1970 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 8-27)
  - Commerce 324-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Economics 331-, 1967 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Economics 332-, 1972 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Economics 333-, 1972 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Commerce 337-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Commerce 343-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Commerce 345-, 1973 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Commerce 346-, 1972 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Economics 351-, 1970 - 1975; F-8-7-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Economics 353-, 1969 - 1975; F-8-7-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Economics 355-, 1972 - 1983; F-8-7-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 8-28)
  - Economics 362-, 1977 - 1984; F-8-7-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 363-, 1967 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 365-, 1972 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 367-, 1967 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 368-, 1967; F-8-7-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Commerce 370-, 1970; F-8-7-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Commerce 371-, 1971 - 1975; F-8-7-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Commerce 373-, 1970 - 1975; F-8-7-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 380-, 1970 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 381-, 1976 - 1981; F-8-7-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 386-, 1973 - 1979; F-8-7-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Commerce 387-, 1971 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 390-, 1970 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Commerce 393-, 1970 - 1980; F-8-7-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 395-, 1972 - 1976; F-8-7-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 8-29)
  - Economics 396-, 1972 - 1976; F-8-7-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 397-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 401-, 1973 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 404-, 1972 - 1973; F-8-7-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 406-, 1972; F-8-7-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 409-, 1970 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 410-, 1972 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 413-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 422-, 1970 - 1971; F-8-7-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 423-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 424-, 1968 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 428-, 1974; F-8-7-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 429-, 1970; F-8-7-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 431-, 1972 - 1973; F-8-7-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 435-, 1974; F-8-7-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 436-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 440-, 1969 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 442-, 1977 - 1978; F-8-7-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 443-, 1969 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 445-, 1967 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 446-, 1970 - 1971; F-8-7-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 449-, 1971; F-8-7-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 455-, 1970 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 465-, 1970 - 1971; F-8-7-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Commerce 478-, 1970 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 8-30)
  - Economics 480-, 1976; F-8-7-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 481-, 1971 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 483-, 1972 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 484-, 1973; F-8-7-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 486-, 1969 - 1972; F-8-7-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Commerce 488-, 1969 - 1974; F-8-7-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 489-, 1971; F-8-7-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 490-, 1970 - 1971; F-8-7-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 491-, 1974; F-8-7-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 492-, 1972 - 1973; F-8-7-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 493-, 1974; F-8-7-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Economics 496-, 1969 - 1976; F-8-7-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - Commerce 498-, 1977; F-8-7-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - M.B.A. 605-, 1981; F-8-7-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
- Publications, 1967 - 1980; F-8-8; 2 cm of textual records
  Series consists of newsletters of the Department of Economics and Commerce and the School of Business Administration and Economics.
  - Department notes, 1967 - 1975; F-8-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 8-31)
  - School notes, 1979 - 1980; F-8-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 8-31)